Our world is host to creatures threatening
humanity that we call monsters.
To protect people from these monsters,
we need those with the sacred
power to create barriers.
These women are saints.
They drive back the monsters
and purify the land.
Their presence is such
a boon to national security
that it is vital to every country
to have at least one saint.
And this land, the Kingdom of Girtonia,
is home to the woman known as the greatest
saint of all time, Philia Adenauer.
Oh, Saint Philia is back?
Right. She went to vanquish monsters
in the northwest, didn't she?
Saint Philia to the rescue as usual, huh?
I reckon that's what makes her
the "greatest ever" or whatnot.
Philia Adenauer is the perfect saint.
There is nothing she cannot do.
However, there is one respect
in which she is lacking.
That's the saint!
Go on. You'd better not offend her.
G-Good day, Saint Philia.
And that is...
her smile.
Good day.
To be a saint is to be a wellspring
of love, cherished by her people.
The Kingdom of Girtonia's 28th Saint
Philia Adenauer
But Philia is a saint who never smiled.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 1
"The Saint Who Never Smiled"
Come again!
Excuse me, sir. Who might
that beautiful woman be?
This your first time in Girtonia?
Yeah.
Guess you wouldn't know, then.
She's our saint.
Girtonia currently has two, in fact!
The other is Saint Mia!
She's so sweet and darling!
The smile she blesses the people of Girtonia
with equally is truly a national treasure!
The kind, charming Saint Mia is beloved by all!
But that one over there...
That's Saint Philia, Saint Mia's elder sister
and purportedly the most gifted in history.
Saint Philia!
About my request from the other day...
The shipping route has been
secured. You can rest easy.
Saint Philia.
Our crops are dying from this drought.
Can't you please make it rain?
Yes, I performed the ritual recently.
It should rain very soon.
I believe I can arrange for regular
rainfall in the future as well.
She can do that?!
Well, well, if it isn't our precious saint.
I wanted to check in about that
medicine I asked you to develop.
I gave her an impossible task!
She could never pull it off, right?
Now, admit your failure
and beg for forgiveness!
I gave the formula to the herbalist just now.
You pulled it off?!
Sounds like Girtonia's saint is amazing.
Yeah. Most of Girtonia's land
is either desert or barren.
Examples of Philia's Achievements
Developing new medicines
Advancements in pharmacology
Subsequently establishing
trade routes
Expanding safe zones
with powerful barriers
Developing new farmland
Cultivating more suitable crops
We don't have a lot of natural resources.
Life used to be real hard.
She's the one who turned everything around.
But she's so good,
she's stepped on some toes,
so there are folks who resent her, too.
I have returned home.
Philia! How long must you waste
on such simple tasks?
Please forgive me, Mother.
You are utterly incompetent.
I see why it took you
so long to become a saint.
You should take a lesson from Mia,
a true genius who completed her
saint training in just one year!
And unlike you, she has a smile
to soothe the souls of all who behold it.
Don't you think she's far closer
to what the people expect of a saint?
Yes.
And then we have you!
Stealing people's work
just to prove yourself...
How haughty and self-concerned
with looking superior!
You have the perfect role model at hand,
so why can't you manage
even a mote of charm?!
Do you realize how insistently
you upset those around you?
And you do it all with that
frighteningly blank expression!
You shame the title of saint!
At tea parties, we hear nothing
but complaints about your attitude!
How do you think that makes us feel?!
Please forgive me.
You should take the time you spend studying
medicine and work on your personality instead!
What scant praise you received for your
talents doesn't justify such arrogance!
Ah, I've done it again...
The way people see you affects
the way they see Mia, too!
Try to behave like her older sister for once.
Yes, Mother.
How did things turn out this way?
A saint's duty is to use
her power for her kingdom.
That's what I was taught. And yet...
The more I've done,
the harder I've worked...
For some reason, I've just
ended up further ostracized.
Be charming? Smile?
I don't understand any of that.
I've never known how to smile.
Perhaps that's what turned
my parents against me.
As I watched them shower
my sister with all their love,
even as a child, I could tell...
"I'm going to have to work
very hard to ever be loved."
Philia Adenauer...
Born to the Adenauer family,
known for producing saints.
She left home to join the church at age five.
She learned etiquette, past and present,
as well as magical and martial arts.
After I learned I was dull
and lacking in charm,
I knew I was going to have
to be exceptional in some way.
Survived alone in the mountains for a month.
My parents enrolled me in saint training,
Buried alive in the desert.
Slept atop a bed of spikes.
and my mentor put me through hell.
You're so useless and dull.
This training is for your benefit.
If you can please us all,
you will finally know love.
"Become the perfect saint.
One who can do anything."
The days I spent in training hell,
in the shadow of that impossible goal...
I was in no shape to smile.
She was certified as a saint at sixteen
and declared the greatest of all time.
Now, at nineteen, she's been
recognized by the king
and engaged to the second prince
of Girtonia, Prince Julius...
Forgive the wait.
I shall take you to His Highness.
If you'd be so kind.
Upon my formal engagement
to Prince Julius,
I thought perhaps my efforts
had at last paid off a little.
I thought I had been acknowledged.
Dad!
Hey!
You came out to meet me?
Yeah! Welcome home, Dad!
Thanks, my boy.
Big Sister! Welcome home!
The Kingdom of Girtonia's 29th Saint
Mia Adenauer
Thank you, Mia.
You're reading in my room again?
Your room is so much more relaxing!
There's just something soothing
about the way it smells!
It's like you're all around me,
and it makes me feel so safe!
I don't really feel at home here,
but Mia's always welcoming.
Though I'd never admit that anywhere else.
They'd say I'm obsessed with you.
It's the only thing that makes
coming back feel worthwhile.
Oh? Big Sister, what's that box?
It's, well...
Rose hairpin
I-Is this for me?!
Did you buy this, Big Sister?!
Yes.
The Product of 10 Years of Studying
A "whatever's edible" and
"whatever's not hideous" mindset
You, who's never cared anything for clothes
or food or music or trends?!
Yet you got this just for me?
I'm so happy! I'll treasure it forever!
So cute.
I know! As thanks, I'll
pick out an outfit for you!
How about something for a
date with Prince Julius?
Maybe tomorrow!
Tomorrow?
As a matter of fact, the prince
wants to see me tomorrow.
A date? Is it a date?!
I don't know.
Well, I can't argue with the prince!
But let's go shopping on your
next day off for sure, Big Sister!
Yes, let's. It's a promise.
My job is hard...
But with Mia in my life,
I know I can weather any storm.
That wretched Philia...
Her attitude is utterly insufferable.
Being called the greatest
of all time has made her arrogant,
yet she's only ever vanquished petty monsters.
She's nothing compared
to the legendary saint
who saved the world from the
legendary archdemon Asmodeus!
True enough.
The Kingdom of Girtonia's Second Prince
Julius Girtonia
Girtonia doesn't need two saints.
Let's put the plan into action.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Oh, it's Saint Mia!
Saint Mia! Do you have the day off?
I do!
That's why I'm out for a walk.
Saint Mia! Hello!
Excuse me!
Saint Mia, thank you for all you do for us!
Oh, thank you so much!
How delightful.
Say, Saint Mia, have you done
something different with your hair?
Yes...
The person I admire most
in the world gave this to me!
I wonder if you've made it
to the castle yet, Big Sister!
Prince Julius...
I wonder why he's summoned me so urgently.
That's our family's carriage.
Is Father here as well?
Good to see you, Philia!
I've never seen him in
such a good mood before.
I heard what you did.
You took initiative and vanquished the
werewolves in the northwest all by yourself.
Yes.
The soldiers are always complaining
about you taking their jobs.
You've even given them advice on formations.
You know that's not a woman's place.
Your Highness...
Are you pleased about something?
Yeah, that's right!
I just got some great news, in fact.
What do you think it is?
Philia Adenauer...
Our engagement is officially terminated!
Could you please elaborate, Your Highness?
Sure.
I've decided to marry Mia instead.
What?
There's something so inhuman and
charmless about being too perfect.
Saints should just stick to praying.
You don't have to be so talented.
Though it's because of my lack
of charm that I sought to be perfect...
Your little sister Mia is
much better in that regard!
She's beautiful, sweet, and has something
special that makes you want to protect her.
If you have to marry a saint of the
Adenauer family, anyone would choose Mia.
That's all there is to it.
Have you informed Mia of this?
No, not yet.
But I could see she was seeking my
favor at that party the other day!
And besides...
He said it was official, remember?
Father, Mother...
It was Prince Julius
who presented us with the idea.
Naturally, we agreed!
Do amicably withdraw in the name
of Mia's happiness, Philia.
She would make a much
better queen, after all!
If...
If this is what Mia really wants...
If it would make her happy...
However...
There's just one problem.
Mia could potentially refuse
out of consideration for you.
Which is why...
Almburg
Elekana
Parnacorta
Girtonia
I've decided to sell you
to our neighbors in Parnacorta!
Wh-What do you mean by that?
Apparently their only saint
passed away suddenly.
I feel bad for them, so I sounded them out...
"Might you be in need of a saint deemed
to be the greatest of all time?"
And what do you think they said?!
They came begging for you, offering
payment tantamount to our annual budget!
I mean, my goodness!
Talk about a fabulous deal for everyone.
Plus, when the public finds out I tearfully
let go of my betrothed for my country,
I'll get a surge in support.
I'll grant 30 percent of the profit
to the Adenauers along with a peerage.
And I'm sure Mia will be
over the moon to marry me.
Indeed, this is going to make everyone happy!
It's going to make... everyone happy?
The one thing I can't understand
is why they'd pay so much for Philia.
It's the first time anyone's seen
worth in you. It's almost strange.
And now our family will enter
the upper echelons of society!
What a noble self-sacrifice
to honor your parents!
We've done a fine job raising you after all.
I suppose you put in a little effort as well.
I've always...
All I've ever done...
was to work hard in hopes
of earning your approval.
Am I not also your daughter?
Farewell, Philia.
I don't imagine we'll ever meet again.
But then... where will I find happiness?
I really have been thrown out.
What should I have done differently?
I guess I'll never know.
There's no fixing any of it now.
Now, all that money
we swindled from Parnacorta...
What should I spend it on?
Perhaps we could erect a golden
statue of you as Girtonia's king!
Really, let's not get ahead of ourselves!
Father is still alive, after all.
But His Majesty has been ill
for quite a long time...
And the first prince, Fernand, has withdrawn
from the public eye out of fear of your power.
I believe your coronation may
come sooner than you think.
And the moment you become king,
your greatness will propel Girtonia
to new heights of prosperity!
Yes, you're right.
I'll have it all.
The throne of Girtonia and Mia.
How long was I asleep?
It's been so long since I had nothing to do.
I don't know what to do with myself.
Almburg
Elekana
Parnacorta
Girtonia
Parnacorta...
I wonder what it's like there.
They apparently paid a lot for me...
I suppose they'll expect
to get their money's worth.
I have to be prepared to work like a slave.
There's nothing to be gained
from fretting over it.
Even if I'm moving elsewhere,
my duty remains the same.
I just need to work hard as a saint.
Work hard? Why am I doing that?
Who and what are the saint's duties for?
This is as far as we can take you.
You can get another carriage
on the other side of the border.
The border...
There's a crowd at the
Parnacorta checkpoint?
Saint Philia has arrived!
Welcome...
to Parnacorta.
What?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 2:
Next Time
Episode 2
"Welcome to Parnacorta"
"Welcome to Parnacorta."